>> Kyle Simpson: 相同类语法。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The same class syntax.
但这就像在糖下面，这就是密码的样子。
But this is like the underneath the sugar,
this is what the code would look like.
这就是以前做原型班的学校方式，所以叫。
This is the old school way of doing
a prototypal class, so called.
你注意到我们有一个工作坊的功能
You notice that we have a workshop
function which is going to serve sort of
构造函数的用途。
the purpose of the constructor.
然后我们开始向 Workshop.prototype 添加方法。
And then we start adding methods
to the Workshop.prototype, and
我们会打新电话之类的
we cog new calls and stuff.
所以你可以看到一些阶级的基础
So you see some of
the underpinnings of classes, but
这就是在等级糖中发生的事情
this is the plumbing underneath what
is happening in the class sugar.
因为如果你想做的话你就不会再写这代码了
It's not that you would really write this
code anymore because if you wanted to do
几乎可以肯定的是使用类语法。
classes at all you almost certainly
be using the class syntax.
你不会再写这个原型代码了但我认为
You wouldn't write this prototypal code
anymore, but I think it's important for
你知道这些水管是怎么工作的
you to understand how this plumbing works.
关系在哪里 ?
Where are the relationships?
这些联系都在哪里 ?
Where are all of those linkages?
因为他们不是拷贝，因为拷贝其实是一个不好的心理模型，
Since they're not copies and since
copying is actually a bad mental model,
我们需要一个不同的心理模型来帮助我们了解等级如何运作，
we need a different mental model that
helps us understand how class works, how
它真的有用，所以我们可以理解它休息的时候，为什么会中断呢 ?
it really works, so that we can understand
when it breaks, why did it break?
为什么它做的事情跟我们预期的不一样 ?
Why did it do something
different than what we expected?